

Javier Giordano Data Scientist Multimedia Designer Web Dev - Digital Artist

Cellphone: 1559301321

E-Mail: javiergiordano@gmail.com

Weh:

https://www.javiergiordano.com.ar/index_eng.html

Linkedin:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/javier-

giordano-789648174



I'm a Data Scientist with a strong business vision, currently focused on digital transformation,

proactive, curious and a fan of cybersecurity, aritfcial vision and IA. I really enjoy researching and learning new technologies to find creative solutions to new challenges.

I consider myself passionate about technology and knowing how the world works, I like to investgate and that is why throughout my career I was able to develop myself in diferent areas, which allows me to have a comprehensive view of things (I'm an eternal student).



EDUCATION

2019	Data Science Career (ACAMICA Inst).
2019	Python for computer vision OpenCV and Deep Learning.
2019	Python for data science and Machine Learning bootcamp.
2018	Machine Learning and Business Intelligence (F. telefónica).
2018	Fundamentals of Computer Hacking.
2018	Responsive Web Development.
2009-2012	Diseño Multimedial (Escuela Davinci).



WORK EXPERIENCE ____

2022 - Curr. GCBA Head of Data analytics and visualization team of the evidence-based public policy secretary.

HSBC Data visualization. Interactive data dashboard for internal management of the transformation team 2020 - 2021

- Made with D3.js DC.js Crossflter.js

2019 - 2022 DameLuna Chief executive. Commercial management and asset management, comprehensive digital

transformation, corporate identity, digital ecosystem, marketing plan, e-commerce development.

La Vía Campesina, Front-end Dev. Design and development of educational platform and interactive content 2018

With geolocation.

2017 Picker Digital Marketing and communication manager. E-commerce development - MercadoLibre integraton,

Social media marketing planner.

2002 La Mar en Coche, Freelance, Web design/dev - Interactive design, technical operator - Motion capture based

games design for social events.

2011 - 2015 Ministerio de Planifcación Federal, inversión pública y Servicios, Team Leader, Theatrical and multiedia

content creator for public

actvities.



IT

Python JavaScript - D3.js Data Analysis - ETL Power Bi - Carto OpenCV - Al Deep/Machine Learning

Web

HTML5 CSS3 Three.is Bootstrap Moodle

Design

Photoshop - Illustrator Blender - Cinema 4D A/V

Adobe After Effects Premiere

Extras

Inglés B1 Unity 3D Cibersecurity/hacking **Realtime Signal Processing Creative Coding**